As I noticed the researchers walking out of the room, uhm,
I was starting to get a little nervous because I wasn't used to this experience.
I realized that when I had hit my tight position, my hands weren't in a fist.
During this moment, I was worried that I didn't have enough snap in my kicking,
and I tried to be more mindful of my footwork, as I didn't want to stumble against my balance.
I noticed how my back stance wasn't as prominent,
And I didn't push my knees out as enough.
This one here, for this timing, or this particular part of the poomsae,
it needed to be a little faster, so I tried to focus on my snapping motion.
I had to twist my wrists a little bit more, but I feel like I was a little too soft.
And during this part of the poomsae, I noticed my body was too close against the camera,
and I needed a little more space for me to proceed with the next movement.
I think I extended my arms a little too far out.
Here, I kind of stumbled against my balance because I went off the mats.
I think during this moment, I was curling my wrists too much,
and I need to punch a little to my stomach area.
Here, I thought my kicks were fine.
I think my timing was okay because when I landed,
my heel touched the ground the same time that I did my elbow strike.
Though I think my hands were a little loose near the end.
And then I felt relieved when I finally ended the poomsae here.